

ABOUT ME

Logistics Engineer with experience in various industries such as transportation, warehousing, digital marketing, and IT. Currently working as a Traffic Assistant at one of the largest digital marketing agencies in Poland. Developing programming skills with a focus on front-end development and technical support. Experienced in HTML, working with JavaScript, and WordPress

SKILLS

English language

B2 - Intermediate

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and WordPress

Intermediate

React.js, PHP, Node.js, Bootstrap

Basic

Microsoft Exce

Advanced

Microsoft Office

Intermediate

Basic

DaVinci Resolve

Driving license

Category B

Forklifts operation UDT qualifications

HOBBIES

Football

Writing lyrics

Graphic

Hiking

Climbing

Traveling

Norbert Sarapata

Logistics engineer / Front-end developer / Traffic assistant

■ E-mail: sarapata.norbert@gmail.com ■ Website: norfeone-design.pl LinkedIn: norbert-sarapata-a2a897224/

L Phone number: +48 664 447 122

GitHub: github.com/Norfeusz # Birth-date: 24 08 1994

Place of living: Cracow

Job experience

Cube Group Warsaw 2024-present

Traffic assistant

Technical support in a digital marketing agency. Coding client creatives, conducting validation, participating in the affiliation process, and troubleshooting issues.
Supporting the development team. Working with Google Tag Manager, Campaign Manager, Ingenious System, and Microsoft Excel.

Jumbo Distribution Center Nieuwegein, Netherlands

Clearing Station Operator, Captain

Production work in a modern, partially automated warehouse in the Netherlands. Managing and supervising the work of an international team. Transfering and executioning of Process Leader's commands. Advising and cooperation with Process Leader. Independent decision making and reacting to dynamic situations. Working in all warehouse departments (in two as a captain).

Leroy Merlin Cracow 2022

2023-2024

Logistics Manager

Organizing work of warehouse employers. Providing optimal and safe flowless of goods between suplier and customer. Providing professional service of customers orders. Taking care of stock levels and warehouse processes.

Uber, Bolt, Freepresent Cracow

2022

Driver

Transportation of clients of popular mobile applications.

Jumbo Distribution Center Nieuwegein, Netherlands

2020-2021

Clearing Station Operator, Captain

Pizzer-man, driver

Making and delivering pizza.

Fabryka Pizzy

Cracow 2018-2020

Delikatesy Extra Cracow 2017-2018

Warehouse logistics

Keeping the warehouse in order. Supervising over the proper storage of resources. Placing and accepting orders. Customer service in the store hall. Arranging and fronting products on store shelves.

Education

MMC School (online) 2023-...

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js

Learning programming languages with the help of certified courses led by Mateusz Maj

University of Economics Cracow

2016-2020

International logistics

Bachelor's Degree in International Logistics.

VII High School Cracow

2010-2013

Mathematics & Physics

"I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, Item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the fine movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/C (General Data Protection Regulation)."